3:Line 7: 'isMenuOpen' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u. (no-unused-vars)
4:Line 7: 'setIsMenuOpen' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u. (no-unused-vars)
5:Line 13: Error: Calling setState synchronously within an effect can trigger cascading renders
20:Line 22: 'navigate' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u. (no-unused-vars)
21:Line 97: Error: Avoid constructing JSX within try/catch
41:Line 114: Error: Avoid constructing JSX within try/catch
52:Line 118: 'e' is defined but never used. (no-unused-vars)
55:Line 180: Error: Avoid constructing JSX within try/catch
75:Line 200: 'e' is defined but never used. (no-unused-vars)
78:Line 5: Fast refresh only works when a file only exports components. Use a new file to share constants or functions between components. (react-refresh/only-export-components)
79:Line 41: 'error' is defined but never used. (no-unused-vars)
80:Line 50: React Hook useEffect has missing dependencies: 'currencies' and 'updateRate'. Either include them or remove the dependency array. (react-hooks/exhaustive-deps)
81:Line 61: 'e' is defined but never used. (no-unused-vars)
84:Line 1: 'useEffect' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u. (no-unused-vars)
85:Line 62: Fast refresh only works when a file only exports components. Use a new file to share constants or functions between components. (react-refresh/only-export-components)
88:Line 15: Error: Calling setState synchronously within an effect can trigger cascading renders
103:Line 16: 'e' is defined but never used. (no-unused-vars)
104:Line 50: Fast refresh only works when a file only exports components. Use a new file to share constants or functions between components. (react-refresh/only-export-components)
107:Line 31: React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 'fetchOrders'. Either include it or remove the dependency array. (react-hooks/exhaustive-deps)
110:Line 21: 'image' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u. (no-unused-vars)
113:Line 109: 'notifyErr' is defined but never used. (no-unused-vars)
114:Line 203: 'notifyErr' is defined but never used. (no-unused-vars)
117:Line 12: 'setSettings' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u. (no-unused-vars)
118:Line 38: 'notifyErr' is defined but never used. (no-unused-vars)
121:Line 32: 'submitting' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u. (no-unused-vars)
122:Line 67: 'handleSubscribe' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u. (no-unused-vars)
123:Line 83: 'err' is defined but never used. (no-unused-vars)
126:Line 63: React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 'fetchReviews'. Either include it or remove the dependency array. (react-hooks/exhaustive-deps)
127:Line 138: 'error' is defined but never used. (no-unused-vars)
130:Line 104: 'orderId' is defined but never used. (no-unused-vars)
133:Line 41: 'isAdmin' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u. (no-unused-vars)
